According to labor law,
you've been working too much, Yachiyo.
The Ten Commandments of Gingarou
1. Aim to be the number one hotel in the galaxy.
2. Food and etiquette are mainstays of culture.
3. Bookmark today's page in our guests' lives.
4. A smile is the ultimate ambiance.
5. Our only vice is service.
6. Tradition evolves with innovation and experimentation.
7. Clean sheets symbolize pure hearts.
8. Provide unlimited hospitality in limited time.
9. Bow down deep but always aim high.
10. A true hotel is always storied.
President, Gingarou Hotel
Tomorrow never dies
Don't count your tanuki
before they hatch
More venom
for the aliens
Groom yourself all
the way to the tail
Wag your tail,
but never
wag a shift!
Fry the Nudels,
not the rooms!!
It's okay to paper over the cracks
with hospitality that rocks
Discipline with a fist!
Reconcile with a high five!
I'm sorry?
I read that overworking employees
can cause long-term issues,
so you need to take time off.
I do understand that much.
But why now, after all this time?
I'm learning all I can about Earth.
Babeh-O told me about a Roppongi
bookstore that was still in good shape.
So I borrowed these.
Labor Standards Law I
Labor Standards Law II
I do see your point. However...
Yeah, yeah.
I bet you're gonna say you don't need
time off because you're a hotelier robot.
Denied!
Even a robot can break from continuous use.
Anyway, you're taking tomorrow
and the day after off.
I'm confiscating your uniform
so you can't work.
Okay, take it off. Step on it, ponchaka.
What does one do on a day off?
Wel—
Welcome to the Gingarou Hotel.
Wecclom to the Gingarou Hotel!
Please come this way.
May I have a room?
Episode 11
Wag Your Tail,
but Never Wag a Shift!
I hear they have something
called a "hot-spring bath."
That sounds good.
Hello there.
Hello.
I wanna check it out before dinner.
Good.
Stains, none.
Droplets, none.
Mold, none.
Amenities, good.
Shampoo hat—
Kamemaru Tech Hotelier Android
Recommended usage limit exceeded.
Malfunctions may have severe
adverse effects on hotel operation.
Please replace part immediately.
Recommended usage limit exceeded.
Malfunctions may have severe
adverse effects on hotel operation.
Please replace part immediately.
Can pets stay at this hotel, too?
Pets are now allowed on the premises.
We do get some runaways, so we ask
that you put a hotel tag on your pet.
My, your service lives up
to the stellar reviews!
My DraDra will stay in my room with me.
Bath-arou
Open
Tangerine Bath
How to Bathe
Wash!
Rinse!
Relax~
Bath
Women's Bath
No compatible spare parts found
If you have a day off, try walking through Ginza,
the town where retro-modern meets the bleeding
edge! You're sure to find something good!
Rinkou Yuudouson
A spiritual sanctuary within
a stone's throw of Ginza!
Prosperity in business
and family health are...
Rinkou Yuudouson
A spiritual sanctuary within
a stone's throw of Ginza!
Prosperity in business
and family health are...
Gingarou Distillery
The Gingarou Hotel's Original Single Malt
Ginga
-exclusive barley farm
We grow it ourselves!
Active Astronaut
No compatible spare parts found
Let's use it as bait!
That was a gift from a guest.
Chill out in the big city!
Time to blaze it!
Smoking Bonus!
Cigarette Butt Rush!
Wag Your Tail, but Never Wag a Shift!
Kamemaru Tech Hotelier Android
Recommended usage limit exceeded.
Malfunctions may have severe
adverse effects on hotel operation.
Please replace part immediately.
Recommended usage limit exceeded.
Malfunctions may have severe
adverse effects on hotel operation.
Please replace part immediately.
Compatible spare
parts in stock
Compatible spare parts found
Damaged component
This component is damaged.
Please recheck all connections and reboot.
For Space Ark
Launch Station
Reparations for all
No discrimination
Save all citizens
Don't stand
for this!
I love peace
Damaged Beyond Repair
Compatible spare parts found
Extra Mission
"Get Bit by a Pegasus" complete.
Easter Egg Program
Extra Mission
"Get Bit by a Pegasus" complete.
New function "Cross-Eyed" unlocked.
Easter Egg Program
Extra Mission
"Get Bit by a Pegasus" complete.
New function "Cross-Eyed" unlocked.
Please rest assured. We'll do everything—
Easy for you to say!
Oh, DraDra! I'm so glad you're safe!
I told you not to go off wandering!
I'm so, so glad!
Yachiyo!
How did you like your time off?
I felt alive.
Translation: Sriram Gurunathan
Editing & Typesetting: Geoff Mazzolini
Subtitle Timing: Mariana Martinez